georgiasown.org 2015-03-17

# FACTS

                                                                                                                        Rev. 07/12
                                                                                                                             12/10
                        WHAT DOES GEORGIA’S OWN CREDIT UNION DO
FACTS                   WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                    Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                        consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we
                        collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand
                        what we do.
What?                   The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have
                        with us. This information can include:
                        - Social Security number and account transactions
                        - credit card or other debt and overdraft history
                        - payment history and transaction history
                        When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this
                        notice.
How?                    All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday
                        business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’
                        personal information; the reasons Georgia’s Own Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you
                        can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information                    Does Georgia’s Own              Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                  Credit Union share?
For our everyday business purposes –                                           Yes                                No
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –                                                   Yes                                No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                             Yes                                No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –                               No                          We don't share
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –                               No                          We don't share
information about your creditworthiness
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                             No                          We don't share
Questions?              Call toll-free 800-533-2062 or go to www.georgiasown.org
                                                                                              DGAEK2 (DXPS00 PNDM01)-e

Page 2
What we do
How does Georgia’s Own Credit  To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
Union protect my personal      security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer
information?                   safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Georgia’s Own Credit  We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Union collect my personal      - open an account or pay your bills
information?                   - apply for a loan or give us your employment information
                               - give us your contact information
                               We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                               affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                               - sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your
                                  creditworthiness
                               - affiliates from using your information to market to you
                               - sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                               State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                     Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                               nonfinancial companies.
                               - Georgia’s Own Credit Union has no affiliates
Nonaffiliates                  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                               nonfinancial companies.
                               - Nonaffiliates we share with can include insurance companies, government
                                  agencies, plastic card processors (credit/debit/ATM), financial statement
                                  publishers or printers, mailhouse, mortgage service companies, consumer
                                  reporting agencies, data processors, and check/share draft printers
Joint Marketing                A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market
                               financial products or services to you.
                               - Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies and service providers.
Other important information
